Some girls would kill to be Cheerleaders.
Cheerleader Camp is a comedy, horror, thriller film directed by John Quinn.
A cheerleader named Alison is plagued by nightmares about the upcoming all-state
finals and attends a summer training camp with her teammates.
When a number of deaths start occurring at the camp, Alison's nightmares turn twisted and
brutal, and she begins to believe that she may be responsible for the mayhem.
Alison Wentworth, played by Betsy Russell.
Brent Hoover, played by Leif Garrett.
Cory Foster, played by Lucinda Dickey.
Bonnie Reed, played by Lorie Griffin.
Pop, played by George Buck Flower.
Pamela Bently, played by Teri Weigel.
Cheerleader Camp is a 1988 American slasher film produced and directed by John Quinn in his
directorial debut, and starring Betsy Russell, Leif Garrett, Lucinda Dickey, and Lorie Griffin.
The film follows a troubled young woman who arrives at a cheerleader summer
camp for a competition, where a series of murders begin to occur.
Production of Cheerleader Camp began in 1987.
It was originally intended to be filmed in Oregon, but was instead shot largely
in Camp Nelson, California, and in the Sequoia National Forest.
The film was given a brief theatrical release in early 1988 under the title Bloody Pom
Poms before Prism Entertainment released it on video in November 1988.
The film explores themes of nightmare, summer camp, cheerleader, mascot, bikini.
The tone is intense and lighthearted and dark.